<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Evictions in NYC</title>
    <link>https://Kerzer.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>John Doe&#39;s personal website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2008–2020, Steve Francia and the Hugo Authors;
All rights reserved.</copyright><atom:link href="https://Kerzer.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Reader Guide</title>
        <link>https://Kerzer.github.io/posts/readers-guide/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://Kerzer.github.io/posts/readers-guide/</guid>
        <description>First step in your exploration of this data set should be to go and look at the map. This map shows Eviction count per council district. The following posts can be explored at will as they each tell a story based on what is seen. You will also be dicreted from the map tab to other stories, but you can come back here to see if you missed anything. If you want to see all the main content click here.</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Map</title>
        <link>https://Kerzer.github.io/posts/map/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://Kerzer.github.io/posts/map/</guid>
        <description>This is the main section where you should do your exploration of how evictions happen in New York City. Before you move on spend a few minutes going through the options in the drop down menu to get a feel for what the map is showing you. When you are ready look below the map to find substories that relate to the most interesting viewings found in the map. Either view the map based on boroughs or with council districts which was the most common seperation of data found for New York City with regards to evictions.</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>General trends</title>
        <link>https://Kerzer.github.io/posts/general_trends/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://Kerzer.github.io/posts/general_trends/</guid>
        <description>Plotly.d3.json(&#34;/map.json&#34;, function(err, fig) { Plotly.plot(&#39;\/map.json&#39;, fig.data, fig.layout, {responsive: true}); }); 
Welcome to the segment about general trends in the dataset. The main topic of this section will be to look at diference between the boroughs to find common denoimnotors across of all of New York City, but also see which boroughs deviate the most. If you have not seen the boroughs in the map go back and enable the right layout in the drop down menu.</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>What happend in 2020?</title>
        <link>https://Kerzer.github.io/posts/2020/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://Kerzer.github.io/posts/2020/</guid>
        <description>Plotly.d3.json(&#34;/map.json&#34;, function(err, fig) { Plotly.plot(&#39;\/map.json&#39;, fig.data, fig.layout, {responsive: true}); }); 
In this section the yearly trend found in the map is explained in greater detail.
Looking at the eviction count for the year 2020 it is alot lower than the previous years. The main reason for this is that evctions were stopped by the goverment because of Covid-19 which struck New York City early on in the pandemic.</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Evictions in bronx</title>
        <link>https://Kerzer.github.io/posts/bronx/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://Kerzer.github.io/posts/bronx/</guid>
        <description>    Plotly.d3.json(&#34;/map.json&#34;, function(err, fig) { Plotly.plot(&#39;\/map.json&#39;, fig.data, fig.layout, {responsive: true}); }); 
Making test text to see if it changes order of what is presented
 General trends What happend in 2020? Go back to the map  </description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Data selection</title>
        <link>https://Kerzer.github.io/posts/data_selection/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://Kerzer.github.io/posts/data_selection/</guid>
        <description>Everything inside of the extra posts can also be found inside our notebook
The main inspiration for this project came from the work concerning crime in San Francisco, which was done in relation to course 02806 about analysis and visualization of data. Based of the two initial projects done in the course one of the main features that stuck out was the use of geojson and plotly to add overlays to maps.</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Genre</title>
        <link>https://Kerzer.github.io/posts/genre/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://Kerzer.github.io/posts/genre/</guid>
        <description>Edward Segel and Jeffrey Heer. Narrative Visualization: Telling Stories with Data
Visual narrative tactics are visual applications which can be used to assist the narrative, which is further subdivided into three segregated sections: visual structuring, highlighting, and transition guidance. We will introduce the tools that we use for data visualization from each of three categories.
  Visual structuring: The concept of visual structuring is related to the narrative structure, and it allows viewers to identify their position within the larger organization of the visualization.</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Discussion</title>
        <link>https://Kerzer.github.io/posts/discussion/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://Kerzer.github.io/posts/discussion/</guid>
        <description>Our data analysis and visualization are based on the evictions dataset of New York that lists pending, scheduled, and executed evictions within the five boroughs from 2017 to the present. There are some advantages of the figures shown in the visualization part.
 First, the visualization has advanced interactivity so that users can easily select the results they are more interested in according to their wishes. Second, to attract the viewer&amp;rsquo;s attention, we try our best to adopt a more beautiful and straightforward way to present the results.</description>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Work Distribution</title>
        <link>https://Kerzer.github.io/posts/work_dist/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://Kerzer.github.io/posts/work_dist/</guid>
        <description>Data selection Genre Discussion Work Distribution  Back to front page</description>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>